

Google Scholar Profile ☐ github.com/yuminsuh yuminsuh.github.io ☑ dltlqqns@gmail.com

I am a researcher at NEC Laboratories America. My current research focuses on efficient models (multi-task models and dynamic networks) and learning visual representation that interacts with language.

### Education

Seoul National University Apr. 2019 – Nov. 2019

Postdoc Advisors: Bohyung Han, Kyoung Mu Lee

Seoul National University

Mar. 2014 – Feb 2019

Ph.D., Electrical and Computer Engineering

Advisor: Kyoung Mu Lee

Seoul National University

Mar. 2011 – Feb. 2013

M.S., Electrical Engineering and Computer Science

Advisor: Kyoung Mu Lee

Seoul National University

Mar. 2007 – Feb. 2011

B.S., Electrical Engineering

Experience

NEC Laboratories America | Media Analytics department December 2019 - Present

Researcher San Jose, CA

Microsoft Research Asia September 2016 – June 2017

Research Intern

Mentors: Jingdong Wang, Tao Mei

Inria | WILLOW team December 2014 – May 2015

Research Intern

Mentors: Minsu Cho, Jean Ponce

# Workshop Organization

# 1st OmniLabel workshop at CVPR 2023 [Workshop][Benchmark][Challenge]

Organizers: Samuel Schulter, Vijay Kumar B G, Yumin Suh, Golnaz Ghiasi, Long Zhao,

Qi Yu, Dimitris N. Metaxas

CVPR 2023

Workshop to promote research on language-based vision perception system beyond simple category names

 $\bullet\,$  New dataset and benchmark for language-based detection

#### Projects

### Generating Enhanced Negatives for Training Language-Based Object Detectors

Shiyu Zhao, Long Zhao, Zhixing Zhang, Vijay Kumar BG, Yumin Suh, Dimitris N Metaxas,

Manmohan Chandraker, Samuel Schulter arXiv 2023

### Improving Pseudo Labels for Open-Vocabulary Object Detection

Shiyu Zhao, Samuel Schulter, Long Zhao, Zhixing Zhang, Vijay Kumar BG, Yumin Suh,

Manmohan Chandraker, Dimitris N Metaxas arXiv 2023

## Papers

#### Efficient Controllable Multi-Task Architectures

Abhishek Aich, Samuel Schulter, Amit K. Roy-Chowdhury, Manmohan Chandraker, Yumin Suh

ICCV 2023

• Dynamic multi-task model that users can precisely control the compute budget and task importance for efficiency

### OmniLabel: A Challenging Benchmark for Language-Based Object Detection

Samuel Schulter, Vijay Kumar B G, Yumin Suh, Konstantinos M. Dafnis\*, Zhixing Zhang\*,

Shiyu Zhao\*, Dimitris Metaxas (\* equal technical contribution, alphabetic order) ICCV 2023 (Oral)

• New dataset and benchmark for language-based detection. Hosted the Omnilabel workshop in CVPR 2023

# Confidence and Dispersity Speak: Characterizing Prediction Matrix for Unsupervised

**Accuracy Estimation** 

Weijian Deng, <u>Yumin Suh</u>, Stephen Gould, Liang Zheng

ICML 2023

Split to Learn: Gradient Split for Multi-Task Human Image Analysis

Weijian Deng, Yumin Suh, Xiang Yu, Masoud Faraki, Liang Zheng, Manmohan Chandraker

**WACV 2023** 

Learning Semantic Segmentation from Multiple Datasets with Label Shifts  Dongwan Kim, Yi-Hsuan Tsai, Yumin Suh, Masoud Faraki, Sparsh Garg, Manmohan Chandraker,  Bohyung Han  • A training scheme to leverage multiple datasets with different label spaces for domain generalization  Controllable Dynamic Multi-Task Architectures	CCV 2022
Dripta S. Raychaudhuri, <u>Yumin Suh</u> , Samuel Schulter, Xiang Yu, Masoud Faraki,	022 (Oral)
On Generalizing Beyond Domains in Cross-Domain Continual Learning Christian Simon, Masoud Faraki, Yi-Hsuan Tsai,Xiang Yu, Samuel Schulter, <u>Yumin Suh</u> , Mehrtash Harandi, Manmohan Chandraker  C	VPR 2022
Cross-Domain Similarity Learning for Face Recognition in Unseen Domain  Masoud Faraki, Xiang Yu, Yi-Hsuan Tsai, <u>Yumin Suh</u> , Manmohan Chandraker  C	VPR 2021
Learning to Optimize Domain Specific Normalization for Domain GeneralizationSeonguk Seo, Yumin Suh, Dongwan Kim, Geeho Kim, Jongwoo Han, Bohyung HanE	CCV 2020
Stochastic Class-based Hard Example Mining for Deep Metric Learning  Yumin Suh, Bohyung Han, Wonsik Kim, Kyoung Mu Lee  • Hard example mining for deep metric learning, applied to image retrieval	VPR 2019
Part-Aligned Bilinear Representations for Person Re-identificiation  Yumin Suh, Jingdong Wang, Siyu Tang, Tao Mei, Kyoung Mu Lee  • Representation learning for person re-identification and image retrieval	CCV 2018
Appearance Dependent Inter-Part Relationship for Human Pose Eestimation  Yumin Suh and Kyoung Mu Lee  APS	SIPA 2016
Discrete Tabu Search for Graph Matching Kamil Adamczewski, <u>Yumin Suh</u> , Kyoung Mu Lee  I	CCV 2015
Subgraph Matching Using Compactness Prior For Robust Feature Correspondence  Yumin Suh, Kamil Adamczewski, Kyoung Mu Lee  C	VPR 2015
Graph Matching via Sequential Monte Carlo'  Yumin Suh, Minsu Cho, Kyoung Mu Lee  E	CCV 2012
Honors and Awards	
<ul> <li>Business Contribution Award, NEC Laboratories America</li> <li>Aiming to realize human digital twins: Image analysis technology that efficiently senses the real world (Press August 2023)</li> <li>NEC develops high-speed, high-precision technology to search for specific persons based on ambiguous appear</li> </ul>	
attribute information by analyzing camera images (Press release, May 2023)  Outstanding Reviewer, CVPR 2023	2023
Outstanding Reviewer, ICML 2020	2023
3rd Place Award, VisDA-2019	2019
• Visual Domain Adaptation Challenge, TASK-CV Workshop in ICCV 2019 with Dongwan Kim, Geeho Kim, Seonguk Seo, Bohyung Han, Taeho Lee, Jongwoo Han, Hyejeong Jeon	
Doctoral Colloquium, KCCV 2019	2019
Doctoral Colloquium, CVPR 2019	2019
<ul> <li>3rd Place Award, SFMI Machine Learning Challenge 2017</li> <li>Challenge on the road sign letter recognition from road view images, Samsung Fire &amp; Marine Insurance, Korea with Jihong Kang and Sungyong Baik</li> </ul>	<b>2017</b>
Graduated with honors (Summa cum laude)	2011

## **Invited Talks**

# Elastic AI for multiple tasks

• Company-wide talk	May 2022
---------------------	----------

• Lomin Inc. Feburary 2022 June 2022

# • Guest lecture in "Moonshot project", Korea University

# Multi-task learning and domain generalization

October 2021 • Australian National University

## Learning local matching for person re-dentification

• Young Research Highlight, Summer Annual Conference of IEIE June 20219

## **Academic Services**

## Area Chair

- CVPR (2024)
- ACCV (2022)

# Senior Program Committee

- AAAI (2022)
- IJCAI (2021)

# Program Committee

- CVPR, ICCV, ICLR, ICML (2023)
- CVPR, ECCV, ICLR, ICML, IJCAI, NeurIPS (2022)
- AAAI, CVPR, ICCV, ICLR, ICML, NeurIPS, WACV (2021)
- AAAI, ACCV, CVPR, ECCV, ICPR, ICML (2020)
- CVPR, ICCV (2019)
- MM (2017)

## Journal Reviewer

• TPAMI, TIP, TMM, TCSVT, CVIU, MMSJ, AOAS

### Student volunteer

• ACCV 2012, MM 2018

## Mentoring

Youngmin Oh (Yonsei University)	2023
Dongwan Kim (Seoul National University)	2023
Abhishek Aich (University of California, Riverside)	2022
Dripta Raychaudhuri (University of California, Riverside)	2021
Weijian Deng (Australian National University)	2020